cpu-upgrade.com 2018-10-03

# CPU-Upgrade: Privacy Policy

### Personal information collected on CPU-Upgrade.com

  * For each web page request our server automatically logs date and time of the request, visitor's IP address, accessed URL, and browser type.
  * We periodically embed analytics script into our web pages. The script collects basic information about your visit and your browser, and reports them back to our server. When provided on the page, the script uses cookies to prevent sending certain information more than once.
  * We run Vertoz and Google AdSense advertisements on the site. Both ad providers track all clicks on the ads, and they may also track visited pages for each site visitor. To serve targeted ads, the providers may store cookies in your browser when you view or click an advertisement. Google AdSense allows you to opt-out of this cookie on [this page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). Please consult Google privacy policy for more information. Vertoz's privacy policy can be found [here](http://www.vertoz.com/privacy-policy).

### How personal information is used

  * Information about all visited pages is used to detect site abuse, such as attempts to scrap content of the site, post spam in our comments or attempts to circumvent site's security. Server log and analytics data is also used to generate site usage reports. Both server and analytics logs are stored on temporary basis and deleted after several months.
  * We do not share any log files and visitors' personal information with third parties.
